Context lives everywhere for us.
>> [music]
>> So for like what I'm building is
it's context lives everywhere, right?
Like you might have stuff that is in
your documents, but when you're doing a
coffee break with your colleague or
going in the elevator, you're also
discussing context there, right? And how
is that going to the AI? So in a way
context lives everywhere for us and
that's what I'm trying to figure out.
These other little piece of context that
live inside of our head that we can
extract by interviews.
>> Yeah.
>> So I think the definition of context is
changing
every day.
>> What would make it safe to push this
agent into the background? Right? And we
we have the infrastructure to do that.
We can run agents in the cloud and
connect them to things. But of course if
we're going to do that, we want to
introduce constraints. Because the only
way we can trust the agents around in
the background is if we constrain the
context and access it has.
>> What are the full pieces of context that
the agent needs?
>> Good question. If the agent knows its
task really well, I think it also knows
really well what it needs. And most of
the time it's us humans telling it, you
know, you need to know this, access to
this. But if your agent can figure out
also what are the additional kind of
documents it might need, then it's
actually telling you, hey, like I want
to do this task. You provided me with
these kind of documents, but can we also
have access to this kind of stuff? If
you can figure that out, then I think
you've got the ultimate context.